Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/g0su13 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Vuetify

Vue.js

Software Development

Nguyen Quang Huy

Software Developer

Hanoi, Hanoi, Vietnam

Summary

My name is Huy, and I specialize in Front-end (FE) and Back-end (BE) web development. My primary tools are React and Node.js, and I've crafted various web applications by leveraging these technologies. Check out my Github for more information about these applications.

Experience

HBLAB Joint Stock Company Software Developer April 2024 - Present (1 year) Quân Cầu Giấy, Hanoi, Vietnam

FPT Software
Frontend Developer
July 2023 - December 2023 (6 months)
Hanoi Capital Region

AVADA Commerce Software Developer April 2023 - June 2023 (3 months) Hà Đông, Hanoi, Vietnam

Education

Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology
Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering · (August 2019 - August 2024)